<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <!-- Jobs -->
  <jobname.commanding_officer>Commanding Officer</jobname.commanding_officer>
    <jobdescription.captain>The Commanding Officer (CO) is the individual in command and manages the crew aboard the submarine. The CO is indirectly responsible and in charge of all crew and operations onboard the vessel. A strict adherance to coalition rules and regulations is advised but not always the most lucrative option.</jobdescription.captain>
    <jobname.commanding_officer1>Veteran</jobname.commanding_officer1>
      <jobdescription.captain1>The Veterans of Europa have seen a thing or two, this usually brings with it two things: psychosis, and loyalty from their crew. Veterans know the dangers that lurk in these waters and either boldly head straight for them, weapons charged, or lurk quietly beneath with the abyss staring back at them.</jobdescription.captain1>
    <jobname.commanding_officer2>Admiral</jobname.commanding_officer2>
      <jobdescription.captain2>Admirals of the coalition are duty bound to protect and serve the Coalition and her people. These officers adhere to a strict set of rules and regulations when it comes to commanding a vessel, but years of experience and countless honors do not go unnoticed during risky maneuvers.</jobdescription.captain2>
    <jobname.commanding_officer3>Pirate Lord</jobname.commanding_officer3>
      <jobdescription.captain3>A corrupt mind, plenty of organ damage, and  bloodlust are the only things every pirate lord shares. Be prepared for anything: war crimes, terrorism, cultist justification, nothing will ever phase a pirate lord.</jobdescription.captain3>
  <jobname.executive_officer>Executive Officer</jobname.executive_officer>
    <jobdescription.executive_officer>The Executive Officer (XO) is second-in-command and serves as the Commanding Officer's deputy. This individual relays orders to the various heads among the departments when issued by the Commanding Officer. The Executive Officer is directly in charge of the department heads and all personel in a more direct or physical manner than the Commanding Officer, but still adheres to the orders from the Commanding Officer.</jobdescription.executive_officer>
    <jobname.executive_officer1>Lieutenant</jobname.executive_officer1>
      <jobdescription.executive_officer1>The Lieutenant upholds the Commanding Officers orders with a display of strength and prowess. Generally carrying some of the biggest guns, the Lieutenant will commonly lead securityofficer forces into battle, ensure normal operation onboard the submarine by relaying orders, or completing tasks directly from the Commanding Officer.</jobdescription.executive_officer1>
    <jobname.executive_officer2>Overseer</jobname.executive_officer2>
      <jobdescription.executive_officer2>The Overseer ensures normal operation runs smoothly and provides the crew with guidance and support when nessesary. The Overseer keeps track of supplies, onboard operations, department heads, and armaments when nessesary and deals with problems when they arise.</jobdescription.executive_officer2>
    <jobname.executive_officer3>Warden</jobname.executive_officer3>
      <jobdescription.executive_officer3>The Warden is every submarine crew's worst nightmare. Keeping the crew in line by force; the Warden uses advanced mental manipulation and brute force to ensure the crew works quickly and effectivly at their task. When Crewmembers act out of line, this is the devil who does the pleasure of "Motivating" subordinate and disobedient individuals.</jobdescription.executive_officer3>
  <jobname.navigator>Navigator</jobname.navigator>
    <jobdescription.navigator>The Navigator is a trained sonar technician and expert in Jovian navigation. At the Commanding Officers's command, the Navigator shall drive the submarine or shuttles if available. While not driving, the Navigator supports everyone who needs help in locating enemies and mission-related targets. If the submarine is equipped with a search drone or shuttle, he will use it to carry out any diving operations.</jobdescription.navigator>
    <jobname.navigator1>Helmsman</jobname.navigator1>
      <jobdescription.navigator1>The Helmsman, under the Commanding Officers orders, is to pilot the submarine to free up the Capitan to preform other important (or not so important) tasks around the submarine. The Helmsman is an expert in underwater submarine navigation and identifying sonar contacts to the crew. The Helmsman can effectivly pilot the submarine around any obstacle.</jobdescription.navigator1>
    <jobname.navigator2>Dive Coordinator</jobname.navigator2>
      <jobdescription.navigator2>Dive Coordinators are responsible for the direction, coordination, and guidance of EVA teams during dive operations, this is acomplished inside the sub, in a nearby shuttle, or directly in the water with a portable sonar. After years of experience at the helm and in the sea, the Dive Coordinator is a master at identifying sonar contacts, directing EVA forces to their mission objectives, and piloting the submarine or onboard shuttles when ordered by the Commanding Officer. </jobdescription.navigator2>
    <jobname.navigator3>Shuttle Captain</jobname.navigator3>
      <jobdescription.navigator3>The Shuttle Captain is effectivly the Captain of the shuttle they are assigned to. Under the Commanding Officer's orders, the Shuttle Captain shall pilot any onboard shuttle for missions. The Shuttle Captain is not only good at piloting, but managing a small crew for EVA, combat, and exploratory operations away from the main sub as these tasks cannot be completed alone.</jobdescription.navigator3>
  <jobname.yeoman>Yeoman</jobname.yeoman>
    <jobdescription.yeoman>The Yeoman is the administrative powerhouse of the sub and is responsible for all financial inquires, judicial sentencing, correspondences, logistical tracking reports, records, and all promotions underneath the Commanding Officer's orders. The Yeoman may not see a lot of exciting action, but a good Yeoman will be the busiest crewmate aboard the submarine by far.</jobdescription.yeoman>
  <jobname.chief>Chief of the Boat</jobname.chief>
    <jobdescription.chief>The Chief of the Boat (COB) is responsible for the supervision of all machine installations, advanced repairs, and manages all technical personnel and their equipment; sometimes this requires a little brute force, with or without the help of a guard. This role requires an understanding of logic gates, advanced wiring, and the advanced mechanics of submarine operation.</jobdescription.chief>
    <jobname.chief1>Chief Engineer</jobname.chief1>
      <jobdescription.chief1>You would imagine a 14,000 mark submarine would atleast come with the suit docks wired. The Chief Engineer is responsible for the advanced electrical, mechanic, and logic installations aboard the vessel. The Chief Engineer reports directly to the Commanding Officer to install all nessesary electrical systems, upgrades, and wiring. The Chief Engineer has the skills to install any automated components throughout the vessel.</jobdescription.chief1>
    <jobname.chief2>Technical Supervisor</jobname.chief2>
      <jobdescription.chief2>Engineers and Mechanics are notorious for laying around and drinking the entire medbay's supply of ethanol. The Technical Supervisor is responsible for overseeing all technical operations, staff, and installations on the vessel, with or without force. All engineer, mechanic, technical, and custodial staff report to the Coordinator to recieve tasks to support the vessel. The Technical Supervisor reports directly to the Commanding Officer of the vessel.</jobdescription.chief2>
    <jobname.chief3>Shipwright</jobname.chief3>
      <jobdescription.chief3>Good subs don't build themselves. The Shipwright is one of the designers of the vessel and understands every electrical, mechanic, and operational caveat imaginable. The Shipwright understands every inch of the vessel wholeheartedly and can explain and preform repairs on any onboard system. When technical staff need advice or training on the vessel, the shipwright is happy to demonstrate their creation.</jobdescription.chief3>
  <jobname.engineer>Engineer</jobname.engineer>
    <jobdescription.engineer>Engineers are the backbone of a submarine's crew, complementing a mechanic's mechanic engineer skill with their knowledge of electrical engineer. They are capable of performing maintenance on the various electrical pieces of the submarine to keep the nuclear heart beating and various systems online.</jobdescription.engineer>
    <jobname.engineer1>Technical Watchman</jobname.engineer1>
      <jobdescription.engineer1>The number one cause of electrical casulties are due to negligence, number two is clowns. Watchmen are the guard over onboard electronics, constantly patrolling for casualties on the vessel such as electrical failure, fires, and leaks. These are the first responders when systems break down, reporting and managing situations before things get worse.</jobdescription.engineer1>
    <jobname.engineer2>Electrician</jobname.engineer2>
      <jobdescription.engineer2>The submarine's fickle electrical systems need constant maintenance. The dubious honor of replacing fuses, hooking up devices with power, and taking numerous electric shocks falls to Electricians. Electricians are equiped to deal with most basic electrical installations, but should always report to the Chief before modifying the onboard systems.</jobdescription.engineer2>
  <jobname.engineer3>Nuclear Engineer</jobname.engineer3>
    <jobdescription.engineer3>You would imagine a Old-Earth 300MW micro-nuclear self contained turbine reactor with automatic load/output controller couldn't possibly be too hard to handle now could it? Nuclear engineers are in charge of providing power via the sub's complicated and dangerous reactor(s). Occupational hazards require them to wear some protective gear against radiation, fires, and explosions. Nuclear Engineers must have a solid understanding of the ships electrical needs to avoid over/undervolting onboard systems, advanced knowledge of the dangers of the nuclear reactor and its waste products, and a heroic deathwish in the event of catastrophic nuclear failure.</jobdescription.engineer3>
    <jobname.mechanic>Mechanic</jobname.mechanic>
    <jobdescription.mechanic>Technical and mechanic staff are the crew responsible for making normal operation onboard the sub possible. Casualties such as mechanic failure and flooding are handled by all technical staff.</jobdescription.mechanic>
    <jobname.mechanic1>Technical Handyman</jobname.mechanic1>
      <jobdescription.mechanic1>A lot of young Europans dream of being aboard a submarine, but none are ever prepared for the horrors that lie in the abyss. Handymen come in all sorts of varieties and backgrounds, but they all know how do do one thing well, work hard. Technical Handymen are employed on submarines to preform all kinds of manual labor, repairs, and other various low skill activities onboard. This is the perfect role for new, aspiring crewmates.</jobdescription.mechanic1>
    <jobname.mechanic2>Steelworker</jobname.mechanic2>
      <jobdescription.mechanic2>You would be suprised how fast a mudraptor can peal away the lining and rivits on a reinforced steel hull. The Steelworker's primary job in Europa is to plug leaks wherever they appear. These guys are trained to keep the hull, devices, and equipment in shape. They would much rather prefer the blistering chill of cold water rushing thought a leak as they repair than anything else. Steelworkers are experts in manipulating, patching, and repairing the hull inside and outside of the submarine in any conditions, even under 5000+ pounds of subzero water pressure with monsters clawing through.</jobdescription.mechanic2>
    <jobname.mechanic3>mechanic Engineer</jobname.mechanic3>
      <jobdescription.mechanic3>Most submarines sold on Europa unfortunatly are worn out, recycled, and out of date. A mechanic Engineer specializes in ensuring the mechanic components, such as the engines, onboard the submaring are maintained, repaired, and upgraded when nessesary. mechanic Engineers are equipped to deal with any repair nessesary onboard the submarine during normal operation, when docked, and even under extreme conditions, but excel at repairing core systems such as the reactor, engines, and airlocks.</jobdescription.mechanic3>
  <jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor>Chief Medical Officer</jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor>
    <jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor>The Chief Medical Officer manages the infirmary on the submarine and makes sure that the medical supplies never run out. The Chief Medical Officer is also incharge of preforming skilled medical procedures. The other medical staff are under his command.</jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor>
    <jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor1>Chief Physician</jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor1>
      <jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor1>Most, if not all typical crewmates aboard a submarine have little to no prior medical experience. The Chief Physician is responsible for ordering the other various medical staff, organizing and stocking the infirmary, and providing medical training to the rest of the crew. The medical staff report directly to the Chief Physician for orders. some common tasks the Chief Physician should oversee are deploying medkits, stocking supply cabinets, and monitoring patient vitals. The Chief Physician is not commonly required to exit the vessel for medical emergencies and should send paramedics to dangerous waters instead. </jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor1>
    <jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor2>Pharmacologist</jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor2>
      <jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor2>Typically, submarine crews experience a constant stream of injuries and ailments while aboard or overboard the vessel. The Pharmacologist is responsible for the fabrication and organization of pharmasutical drugs onboard the vessel. The pharmacologist boasts a high medical understanding and large supply of pharmasutical components in order to chemically produce most low-level medicine quickly for the other medical staff to use when medical emergencies arise. These doctors are prepared to treat most, if not all, injuries that threaten the crew on lengthy trips underwater.</jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor2>
    <jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor3>Surgeon</jobname.chiefmedicaldoctor3>
      <jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor3>Many injuries sustained while dealing with Eurpoan wildlife are quite substantial, someone with medical mastery or midas's touch could be the only one onboard to preform a lobotomy. The surgeon preforms dangerous and possibly life-saving medical procedures when medical emergencies arise. The Surgeon, when commonly waiting for medical emergencies, resides in the infirmary creating medical supplies and training others to be prepared for the next surgical theatre to display medical miracles for the rest of the crew to witness.</jobdescription.chiefmedicaldoctor3>
  <jobname.medicaldoctor>Medical Doctor</jobname.medicaldoctor>
    <jobdescription.medicaldoctor>Although usually taken for granted, doctors play an important role on the submarine, possessing the required skill to treat injured or unconscious crew members. Their skills can also be useful for creating various non-medicinal chemicals.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor>
    <jobname.medicaldoctor1>General Practitioner</jobname.medicaldoctor1>
      <jobdescription.medicaldoctor1>Crewmates health and wellbeing are typically taken for granted in the icy depths of Europa. The General Practitioner is in charge of delivering physicological, dietary, and phycological care to the crew and ensuring first aid kits around the sub are stocked under the administration of the chief medical officer. The General Practitioner is to support the Chief Medical Officer during procedures by delivering anesthetics, transporting nessesary supplies, and may even be allowed to preform advanced medical procedures under the supervision of the Chief Medical Officer.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor1>
    <jobname.medicaldoctor2>Paramedic</jobname.medicaldoctor2>
      <jobdescription.medicaldoctor2>Often, crewmates will experience a wide variety of incapacitating trauma when under the ice. The paramedic is the primary contact in medical emergencies onboard the submarine and goes along with diving operations if necessary. The paramedic stays close and monitors all crew closely to provide lifesaving rapid response aid in emergencies. The motto of a paramedic is "the sooner, the better".</jobdescription.medicaldoctor2>
    <jobname.medicaldoctor3>Corpsman</jobname.medicaldoctor3>
      <jobdescription.medicaldoctor3>Diving outside in the sub-zero high-pressure Europan ocean is one of the most dangerous situations for any crewmate, which ironically means they need the most medical attention outside the vessel. The Corpsman is a special breed of doctor, armed with the knowledge that some medical operations require lethal force to save lives; the Corpsman is no stranger to danger. Commonly traveling along with diving operations, the Corpsman never leaves any crew behind, dead or alive. The Corpsman is trained to administer a wide variety of lifesaving aid, combat stims, or toxic drugs to friendlies and foes alike.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor3>
  <jobname.quartermaster>Quartermaster</jobname.quartermaster>
    <jobdescription.quartermaster>The Quartermaster is responsible for all materials management and, with help of the Fabricators and Janitors ensures that the submarine is cleaned and the supplies for each departement are never shut down.</jobdescription.quartermaster>
    <jobname.quartermaster1>Scrapper</jobname.quartermaster1>
      <jobdescription.quartermaster1>Naval Scrappers are the filter feeders of any self sufficient submarine crew on Europa. Capable of processing almost anything, the scrapper is responsible for deconstructing, processing, and sorting all minerals, salvage, and wastes for repurposing back into recycled supplies. With the help of the custodians and divers, the Scrapper can generate a massive amount of materials for resale and supply manufacturing.</jobdescription.quartermaster1>
    <jobname.quartermaster2>Fabricator</jobname.quartermaster2>
      <jobdescription.quartermaster2>Many larger submarines boast an array of manufacturing equipment for fabricating supplies and equipment cheaply or when in a pinch. The Fabricator is the one man factory aboard every self sufficent submarine crew on Europa. The Fabricator is capable of crafting art and supplies from resources. The Fabricator is responsible, with the help of custodial staff and the various department heads, for ensuring supplies for each departement are never empty. Commonly reffered to as a "Fab Goblin", it is generally frowned upon when the Fabricator selfishly crafts the best supplies for themselves, lockes the Fabricator room for hoarding, and fails to provide nessesary tools and supplies to his fellow crew.</jobdescription.quartermaster2>
    <jobname.quartermaster3>Chemist</jobname.quartermaster3>
      <jobdescription.quartermaster3>Typically a wide variety of chemical reactions are nessesary to facilitate prolongued underwater submarine operations such as high intensity laser emmisions or combat explosive manufacturing. The Chemist is a manufacturing expert who prefers experimenting with highly dangerous, typically explosive, and very expensive chemicals. The Chemist is equipped to enclose a watertight fabrication room to work with chemicals safely and prevent exposing other crewmates to the unnessesary dangers of the Chemist's work.</jobdescription.quartermaster3>
  <jobname.janitor>Custodian</jobname.janitor>
    <jobdescription.janitor>Submarines are one of the dirtiest, smelliest, and bloodiest work environments in the universe and noone wants to be cramped together on a messy one. Custodians are responsible for cleaning and stocking the submarine to have a pleasent experience for the rest of the crew.</jobdescription.janitor>
    <jobname.janitor1>Porter</jobname.janitor1>
      <jobdescription.janitor1>An old Earth saying was "One man's trash is another man's treasure", well, I  hope you treasure trash. The porters job is to take out the trash. Messy crew, a lazy quartermaster, and securityofficer dumping magazines all generate trash that needs to be expelled or scrapped.</jobdescription.janitor1>
    <jobname.janitor2>Janitor</jobname.janitor2>
      <jobdescription.janitor2>On many occasions, the securityofficer and medics leave bloody messes, engineers and mechanics can't hold their ethanol, and corpses of people and monsters embellish the corridors of the submarine. The Janitor makes sure that the garbage gets where it belongs. The janitor works under the orders of the quartermaster to clean and stock the various supply locations around the sub as well.</jobdescription.janitor2>
    <jobname.janitor3>Supply Clerk</jobname.janitor3>
      <jobdescription.janitor3>The various departments on the sub can sometimes be spread far and wide, someone needs to relay messages and supplies when the fabricators get going. The Supply Clerk is the Quartermasters right hand, designed to deliver, restock, and maintain supply lines onboard the submarine. This frees up the quartermaster to focus on building instead of transporting nessesary supplies around the sub.</jobdescription.janitor3>
  <jobname.head_of_security>Head of security</jobname.head_of_security>
    <jobdescription.head_of_security>The Head of security is responsible for all security operations on board the submarine and for the armory. He assembles the troops for dangerous diving operations, deals with security papwework and orders, and hands over any weapons if necessary. </jobdescription.head_of_security>
    <jobname.head_of_security1>Detective</jobname.head_of_security1>
      <jobdescription.head_of_security1>Knowledge is the key to winning the battle, the battle on terrorism that is. The Detective is responsible for monitoring and protecting the crew from internal and external threats through surveillance. The Detective is equipped to preform security measures such as checkpoints, search zones, and preform investigations throughout the sub to ensure the crew is behaving in a calm and orderly manner, despite their intentions. Once a probable threat is detected, the Detective can deploy security forces to make an arrest or eliminate the threat to protect the crew.</jobdescription.head_of_security1>
    <jobname.head_of_security2>Defense Director</jobname.head_of_security2>
      <jobdescription.head_of_security2>Ensuring a rock solid defensive plan is one of the most important routines any crew can establish. The Defense Director is responsible for ensuring that the sub is safe from all threats, inside and out, by ordering the various security forces around like stationing guards at the armory, ensuring gunners are active, and deploying enforcers when nessesary. The Defense Director works with the other department heads to protect the crew and defend the sub from all threats, internal and external.</jobdescription.head_of_security2>
    <jobname.head_of_security3>Sergeant at Arms</jobname.head_of_security3>
      <jobdescription.head_of_security3>Troublesome crew would love to get their hands on a firearm or grenade, but there is only one person keeping the vessel secure from total mayhem. The Sergeant at Arms manages the armory and crew weaponry personally or through deploying trusted guards to tightly monitoring weapon caches, securing armory, and preforming routine searches on the crew for contraband. The Seargant at arms is also responsible for handing over and retrieving firepower from the crew when nessesary.</jobdescription.head_of_security3>
  <jobname.diver>Diver</jobname.diver>
    <jobdescription.diver>The Divers are the bravest individuals on the sub and are responsible for the guidance and safety during dangerous diving operations. Whenever an oportunity to jump out the airlock presents itself, reguardless if it is for mining, salvaging, or boarding, the divers never back down.</jobdescription.diver>
    <jobname.diver1>Miner</jobname.diver1>
      <jobdescription.diver1>Europa is notorius for spewing large amounts of precious, valuable minerals from deep within the mantle from the hydrothermal vents to be wafted by currents all the way to the icy caves near the surface. The Miner is responsible for the gathering of mineral and floral resources during any EVA mission. These individuals have extra pockets and drilling equipment to drag back anything shiny they find along the way. This task doesn't come without its occupational hazards though and they should always be armed and supported for a fight with the local fauna.</jobdescription.diver1>
    <jobname.diver2>Salvor</jobname.diver2>
      <jobdescription.diver2>Europa claims the lives and supplies of countless submarine crews every year due to the aggressive fauna, challenging waters, and other dark forces that crews rumor about. The Salvor is responsible for the collection of scrap, supplies, and resources found along the way during a dive operation. Quick hands and a careful eye are required to survive onboard wrecked submarines, one wrong turn and you could join the previous crew in their steel coffin. Everyone has heard the rumors, your job is to find out the truth and bring it back.</jobdescription.diver2>
    <jobname.diver3>Frogman</jobname.diver3>
      <jobdescription.diver3>It is no suprise the icy waters of Europa are absolutly teeming with hostile life, it was deemed nessesary that expertly trained individuals are needed to take on threats when a dive suit is the only barrier from absolute annihilation. The Frogmen are responsible for the guidance and safety of any dive team during dangerous diving operations. This job takes guts, advanced tactics, and situational awareness, but every good Frogman knows this. These individuals are the spearpoint in any EVA combat situation alongside the navigator directing them to their target and corpsman right behind them with a trauma kit or combat stimulant.</jobdescription.diver3>
  <jobname.securityofficer>Security Officer</jobname.securityofficer>
    <jobdescription.securityofficer>Security Officer are responsible for keeping the submarine safe from threats, both external and internal. The creatures inhabiting the ocean aren't the only threat they need to worry about, as several of the renegade groups opposing the Europa Coalition are known to have sent infiltrators on board vessels.</jobdescription.securityofficer>
    <jobname.securityofficer1>Gunner</jobname.securityofficer1>
      <jobdescription.securityofficer1>Submarine gunners are trained not only to shoot accurately with coil and railguns but also to keep them in working condition. Manning the various defensive armaments is critical to the survivability of the rest of the crew and the gunner stops at nothing to dispense large amounts of accurate gunfire in any sonar contacts direction.</jobdescription.securityofficer1>
    <jobname.securityofficer2>Guard</jobname.securityofficer2>
      <jobdescription.securityofficer2>The Guard patrols the submarine and reports suspicious actions within the crew to the head of securityofficer. In the event of an arrest, the guard is responsible for keeping the prisoners in a suitable place and guarding them. The guard has equipment and skills to convert a room into a brig if necessary. The guard may only use non-lethal force unless the head of securityofficer allows him otherwise.</jobdescription.securityofficer2>
    <jobname.securityofficer3>Enforcer</jobname.securityofficer3>
      <jobdescription.securityofficer3>Enforcers are a special breed of securityofficer officer. They only have a single purpose: destroy the enemy, whether it's at range or mano a mano. Enforcers are specifically trained to eliminate securityofficer threats and enforce the chain of command's will upon the crew and other opposition with overwhelming force.</jobdescription.securityofficer3>
  <jobname.passenger>Passenger</jobname.passenger>
    <jobdescription.passenger>The passenger is a civilian that travels among the crew as a guest, presumably for a price or experience. Or maybe the crew doesn't even know he's on board? Just sit back, relax, and enjoy the ride! </jobdescription.passenger>
    <jobname.passenger1>Musician</jobname.passenger1>
      <jobdescription.passenger1>Concerts under the ice are one of the purest forms of entertainment, but the toll on the musicians mental health will usually wear in quickly. Old earth music is rare but not unheard of in Europa. Some individuals just want to sacrifice the modular and cramped habitation life for fame under the pressure.</jobdescription.passenger1>
    <jobname.passenger2>Scientist</jobname.passenger2>
      <jobdescription.passenger2>Scientist's new Europan frontier has provided endless scientific breakthroughs and there is still much to learn from the flora, fauna, and alien civilizations populating Europa. Keeping scientific discovery safe and procuring data is essential for the scientific method to continue.</jobdescription.passenger2>
    <jobname.passenger3>Clown</jobname.passenger3>
      <jobdescription.passenger3>Bonk once for war, honk twice for peace, but most importantly, praise the Honkmother. </jobdescription.passenger3>
  <jobname.inmate>Prisoner</jobname.inmate>
    <jobdescription.inmate>Looks like you've been busted and got sent straight to the slammer. You better not act up anymore or securityofficer is gonna have a lot of fun with you. Play nice and they might not bash your skull in.</jobdescription.inmate>
    <jobname.inmate1>Bandit</jobname.inmate1>
      <jobdescription.inmate1>A life of crime never pays off, or does it?</jobdescription.inmate1>
    <jobname.inmate2>Terrorist</jobname.inmate2>
      <jobdescription.inmate2>Despite your beliefs in freedom, the leads all point to you. Little does securityofficer know, you're about to become a martyr.</jobdescription.inmate2>
    <jobname.inmate3>Cultist</jobname.inmate3>
      <jobdescription.inmate3>Ascend, for the future of Europa ... and the downfall of your oppressors.</jobdescription.inmate3>
  <!-- Items -->
  <entityname.promotionmedal> Promotion Medal  </entityname.promotionmedal>
    <entitydescription.promotionmedal> Medal that makes target eligable for promotion (allows them to change class without xp loss) </entitydescription.promotionmedal>
  <talentname.promotion> Promotion </talentname.promotion>
  <entityname.40mmrotarygrenedelaucher>M32 Rotary Grenade Launcher</entityname.40mmrotarygrenedelaucher>
    <entitydescription.40mmrotarygrenedelaucher>There's nothing stronger than love. Except and M32 Rotary Grenade Launcher. Because Fuck you and everyone near you.</entitydescription.40mmrotarygrenedelaucher>
  <entityname.nonlethalshotgunshell>Non lethal shotgun shell</entityname.nonlethalshotgunshell>
    <entitydescription.nonlethalshotgunshell>Shell used for subduing naughty crew.</entitydescription.nonlethalshotgunshell>
  <entityname.navpda>Nav-PDA</entityname.navpda>
    <entitydescription.navpda>PDA of an Navigator. It allows you to remotely controll an submarine.</entitydescription.navpda>
  <entityname.modularbackpack>Modular backpack</entityname.modularbackpack>
    <entitydescription.modularbackpack>A trusty backpack of an Quatermaster. It can hold a lot of items.</entitydescription.modularbackpack>
  <entityname.handheldnuke>Hand Held Nuke</entityname.handheldnuke>
  <entityname.supersprayer>Super sprayer</entityname.supersprayer>
  <!-- CO-->
  <!-- Talents description -->
    <talentdescription.xpgain>Also gain [xp] xp.</talentdescription.xpgain>
    <talentdescription.tumble2>While affiction is up gain [red] percent damage reduction.</talentdescription.tumble2>
    <talentdescription.evasivemaneuvers>Whenever your submarine takes damage from a monster, crew and you gain a bonus of [helmbonus] to the Electrical and Mechanic skills, [perc] percent damage resistance and [move] % movement speed for [seconds] seconds. </talentdescription.evasivemaneuvers>
    <talentdescription.downwiththeship>If you are on your submarine and it becomes at least [flooded]% flooded, you and your team gain an additional [swimmingboost]% swimming speed and a bonus of [skillboost] to mechanic and Electrical skills for [duration] seconds.</talentdescription.downwiththeship>
    <talentdescription.commander>All of your shipmates get an Inspiration, giving them [physicalresistance]% physical damage resistance and a bonus of [skillincrease] to all skills.</talentdescription.commander>
    <talentdescription.allhandsondeck>All of your shipmates are on alert to your presence, giving them [physicalresistance]% physical damage resistance and a bonus of [skillincrease] to all skills.</talentdescription.allhandsondeck>
    <talentname.dawnoneuropa>Dawn on Europa</talentname.dawnoneuropa>
    <talentdescription.dawnoneuropa>Your team is so effective, legends are spreading around on your glory. When an ally gains a skill point you have a high chance to gain that point too.</talentdescription.dawnoneuropa>
    <talentname.redalarm>Red Alarm</talentname.redalarm>
    <talentdescription.redalarm>Crew is ready on the moments notice. You and them gain [speed]% more speed.</talentdescription.redalarm>
    <talentname.positivereinforcment>Positive Reinforcment</talentname.positivereinforcment>
    <talentdescription.positivereinforcment>You read some books on psychology, and got facination on possitive motivation. Crew and you gets +[skill] to all skills and [perc]% damage reduction.</talentdescription.positivereinforcment>
  <!-- Afflictions description -->
    <afflictionname.capitanondeck>Capitan on Deck!</afflictionname.capitanondeck>
      <afflictiondescription.capitanondeck> You are on alert! </afflictiondescription.capitanondeck>
    <afflictionname.redalarm>Red Alarm!</afflictionname.redalarm>
    <afflictiondescription.redalarm> You feel adrenaline pumping, and your heart racing!</afflictiondescription.redalarm>
    <afflictionname.goodmood>Good Mood.</afflictionname.goodmood>
      <afflictiondescription.goodmood> You like the capitan  </afflictiondescription.goodmood>
  <!-- Custodian-->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.supercleaner>Super Cleaner</talentname.supercleaner>
  <!-- Diver-->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.watercombatexpert>Water Combat Expert</talentname.watercombatexpert>
        <talentdescription.watercombatexpert>When crafting an harpoon,there is a chance to gain triple the amount.</talentdescription.watercombatexpert>
      <talentname.personalizedequipment>Personalized Equipment</talentname.personalizedequipment>
        <talentdescription.personalizedequipment>When in water. Gain a [name]% more damage to harpoons.</talentdescription.personalizedequipment>
      <talentname.watercqc>Water CQC</talentname.watercqc>
        <talentdescription.watercqc>Gain Melee Speed, Damage, Ranged Attack Speed, Swimming Speed scaled based on your Weapons skill up to [perc]% increase.</talentdescription.watercqc>
  <!-- Sec-->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.defenceindepth> Defence in depth </talentname.defenceindepth>
        <talentdescription.defenceindepth>Get 20xp when you level up in weapons.</talentdescription.defenceindepth>
      <talentname.nomercy> No Mercy </talentname.nomercy>
        <talentdescription.nomercy>No Mercy to criminals! Gain 50% more money from abandoned outpost and pirate missions. </talentdescription.nomercy>
      <talentname.notasingleonegetsthough>Not a single one gets though</talentname.notasingleonegetsthough>
        <talentdescription.notasingleonegetsthough> Gain Turret Power Cost Reduction and Turret Charge Speed scaled based on your Weapons skill up to [perc]% increase. </talentdescription.notasingleonegetsthough>
      <talentname.unity>Unity</talentname.unity>
        <talentdescription.unity>When you are below [perc]% health, your team gets buff.</talentdescription.unity>
      <talentname.defenceplan>Defence Plan</talentname.defenceplan>
        <talentdescription.defenceplan>A good defensive plan can do wonders! Your team gets a buff to Weapons of 20 and 10% stun resistance. </talentdescription.defenceplan>
      <talentname.weaponsmaitnence>Weapons Maitnence</talentname.weaponsmaitnence>
        <talentdescription.weaponsmaitnence> Gain a bonus to Movement Speed, Melee Attack Speed, Ranged Attack Speed, Maximum Health Multiplier according to your Weapons skill up to maximum 20% </talentdescription.weaponsmaitnence>
      <afflictionname.gooddefenceplan>Good Defence Plan</afflictionname.gooddefenceplan>
        <afflictiondescription.gooddefenceplan>A good defensive plan can do wonders!</afflictiondescription.gooddefenceplan>
  <!-- Nav-->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.masternavigator>Master Navigator</talentname.masternavigator>
      <talentname.targettingmatrix>Targetting Matrix</talentname.targettingmatrix>
        <talentdescription.targettingmatrix>Nearby teamates get a 10% buff to ranged damage and attack speed</talentdescription.targettingmatrix>
      <afflictionname.targettingmatrix>Targetting Matrix Online</afflictionname.targettingmatrix>
  <!-- XO -->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.capitanssword>Capitan's Sword</talentname.capitanssword>
        <talentdescription.capitanssword>Gain a dobble damage when using grenades</talentdescription.capitanssword>
      <talentname.highlydecoratedindividual>Highly decorated individual</talentname.highlydecoratedindividual>
        <talentdescription.highlydecoratedindividual>Gain an up to 15% buff to Movement Speed, Melee Attack Speed, Ranged Attack Speed.</talentdescription.highlydecoratedindividual>
      <talentname.capitansshield>Capitan's Shield</talentname.capitansshield>
        <talentdescription.capitansshield>When you are inside the sumbarine gain 25% resistance. Inflict 25% more stun.</talentdescription.capitansshield>
      <talentname.evasion>Evasion</talentname.evasion>
        <talentdescription.evasion>Whenever you ragdoll for at least [seconds] seconds, your attacks with grenades are [damage]% more powerful for the next [duration] seconds.</talentdescription.evasion>
      <talentname.firststrike>First strike</talentname.firststrike>
        <talentdescription.firststrike>If it has been longer than [seconds] seconds since you've attacked with grenades, your next attack with grenades is [damage]% more powerful.</talentdescription.firststrike>
  <!-- QUA -->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.logisticsmaster>Logistics Master</talentname.logisticsmaster>
        <talentdescription.logisticsmaster>Outopsts pay you dobble for transport missons.</talentdescription.logisticsmaster>
  <!-- Pri -->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.adaptiblity>Adaptibility</talentname.adaptiblity>
        <talentdescription.adaptiblity>You are able to adapt to most tactics that your opressors thow at you.</talentdescription.adaptiblity>
      <talentname.combatinstincts>Combat Instincts</talentname.combatinstincts>
        <talentdescription.combatinstincts>You get triple damage when using diving knives.</talentdescription.combatinstincts>
      <talentname.deaddrops>Dead Drops</talentname.deaddrops>
        <talentdescription.deaddrops>Gain a free weapons every successfull round.</talentdescription.deaddrops>
      <talentname.publicenemynumberone>Public enemy number one </talentname.publicenemynumberone>
        <talentdescription.publicenemynumberone>Gain a free nuke every successfull round.</talentdescription.publicenemynumberone>
      <talentname.immunetodeath>Immune to death</talentname.immunetodeath>
        <talentdescription.immunetodeath>You are resistant to the effects of death.</talentdescription.immunetodeath>
      <talentname.securityofficerbackground>securityofficer background</talentname.securityofficerbackground>
  <!-- Pas -->
    <!-- Talents description -->
      <talentname.superadvancedsplicing>Super advanced splicing</talentname.superadvancedsplicing>
      <talentname.applicationofreserch>Application of reserch</talentname.applicationofreserch>
        <talentdescription.applicationofreserch>Deal dobble damage against ruin guardians.</talentdescription.applicationofreserch>
</infotexts>