<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
	<displayname.uesmcalternatewarsuit>[itemname] (Weld helmet)</displayname.uesmcalternatewarsuit>
	<!--
	<entityname.REPLACEMENAME>REPLACEME</entityname.REPLACEMENAME>
	<entitydescription.REPLACEMEDESC>REPLACEME</entitydescription.REPLACEMEDESC>
	
	-->
	
	<!-- Warsuit seperated -->
	<entityname.warsuitr>A.B.Y.S.S. WarSuit body</entityname.warsuitr>
	<entitydescription.warsuitr>The latest 'WarSuit' mixes technologies from all the available diving suits in the market. Ergonomics of the original, plates of the combat variant, and pressure dampers from the abyss diver.</entitydescription.warsuitr>
	<entityname.warsuithr>A.B.Y.S.S. WarSuit helmet</entityname.warsuithr>
	<entitydescription.warsuithr>The latest 'WarSuit' mixes technologies from all the available diving suits in the market. Ergonomics of the original, plates of the combat variant, and pressure dampers from the abyss diver.</entitydescription.warsuithr>	

	<!-- Warsuit fullsuit -->
	<entityname.warsuitrfull>A.B.Y.S.S. WarSuit Full suit</entityname.warsuitrfull>
	<entitydescription.warsuitrfull>The latest 'WarSuit' mixes technologies from all the available diving suits in the market. Ergonomics of the original, plates of the combat variant, and pressure dampers from the abyss diver.</entitydescription.warsuitrfull>
	<entityname.warsuitrnpc>A.B.Y.S.S. WarSuit Full suit</entityname.warsuitrnpc>
	<entitydescription.warsuitrnpc>The latest 'WarSuit' mixes technologies from all the available diving suits in the market. Ergonomics of the original, plates of the combat variant, and pressure dampers from the abyss diver.</entitydescription.warsuitrnpc>
	
	<!-- Composts -->
	<entityname.warsuitdscompost>Diving suit compost</entityname.warsuitdscompost>
	<entitydescription.warsuitdscompost>The first step to recycle the required skeleton for a warsuit. Can be used directly as a component for the full suit, or deconstructed for the separated pieces.</entitydescription.warsuitdscompost>
	<entityname.warsuitcdscompost>Combat diving suit compost</entityname.warsuitcdscompost>
	<entitydescription.warsuitcdscompost>The first step to recycle the required combat components for a warsuit. Can be used directly as a component for the full suit, or deconstructed for the separated pieces.</entitydescription.warsuitcdscompost>
	<entityname.warsuitdadscompost>Abyss diving suit compost</entityname.warsuitdadscompost>
	<entitydescription.warsuitdadscompost>The first step to recycle the required pressure components for a warsuit. Can be used directly as a component for the full suit, or deconstructed for the separated pieces.</entitydescription.warsuitdadscompost>
	
	<!-- Components -->
	<entityname.warsuitframe>Warsuit frame</entityname.warsuitframe>
	<entitydescription.warsuitframe>A skeletonized diving suit, the bones of a warsuit. Obtained by deconstructing a diving suit compost.</entitydescription.warsuitframe>
	<entityname.warsuitpadding>Warsuit combat patch</entityname.warsuitpadding>
	<entitydescription.warsuitpadding>Strong sheets of metal with a much softer inside, these are the shields of a warsuit. Obtained by deconstructing a combat diving suit compost.</entitydescription.warsuitpadding>
	<entityname.warsuitdampers>Warsuit dampers</entityname.warsuitdampers>
	<entitydescription.warsuitdampers>Dampers allow quick adaptation to constant pressure, handy when the world is made out of water. Obtained by deconstructing an abyss diving suit compost.</entitydescription.warsuitdampers>

	<entityname.warsuithelmetframe>Warsuit helmet frame</entityname.warsuithelmetframe>
	<entitydescription.warsuithelmetframe>A skeletonized diving helmet, the skull of a warsuit. Obtained by deconstructing a diving suit compost.</entitydescription.warsuithelmetframe>
	<entityname.warsuitglass>Warsuit bullet proof glass</entityname.warsuitglass>
	<entitydescription.warsuitglass>Bulletproof just means anything that tries to bite your face is going to have a much harder time. Obtained by deconstructing a combat diving suit compost.</entitydescription.warsuitglass>
	<entityname.warsuitpress>Warsuit pressurizer</entityname.warsuitpress>
	<entitydescription.warsuitpress>Keeping the water outside is one of multiple problems, keeping pressure to human-like levels is also vital for underwater ops. Obtained by deconstructing an abyss diving suit compost.</entitydescription.warsuitpress>
	
	<!-- B-Rods -->
	<entityname.marinebatteryrodr>B-Rod</entityname.marinebatteryrodr>
	<entitydescription.marinebatteryrodr>A powerful rod for an equally powerful suit, rechage it at a charging dock or submarine battery. Although it uses the components from the rod, it doesn't deplete it; instead it uses the elecetronic current from the batteries for most of the heavy lifting.</entitydescription.marinebatteryrodr>
	<entityname.marinethoriumbatteryrodr>Focused B-Rod</entityname.marinethoriumbatteryrodr>
	<entitydescription.marinethoriumbatteryrodr>Inceases Psychosis resistance. A powerful rod for an equally powerful suit, rechage it at a charging dock or submarine battery. Although it uses the components from the rod, it doesn't deplete it; instead it uses the elecetronic current from the batteries for most of the heavy lifting.</entitydescription.marinethoriumbatteryrodr>
	<entityname.marinefulguriumbatteryrodr>Energised B-Rod</entityname.marinefulguriumbatteryrodr>
	<entitydescription.marinefulguriumbatteryrodr>Increases Walk and swim speeds. A powerful rod for an equally powerful suit, rechage it at a charging dock or submarine battery. Although it uses the components from the rod, it doesn't deplete it; instead it uses the elecetronic current from the batteries for most of the heavy lifting.</entitydescription.marinefulguriumbatteryrodr>
	<entityname.marinedecoybatteryrodr>Taunted B-Rod</entityname.marinedecoybatteryrodr>
	<entitydescription.marinedecoybatteryrodr>Greatly increases defenses, but creatures preffer you as a meal. A powerful rod for an equally powerful suit, rechage it at a charging dock or submarine battery. Although it uses the components from the rod, it doesn't deplete it; instead it uses the elecetronic current from the batteries for most of the heavy lifting.</entitydescription.marinedecoybatteryrodr>
	<entityname.marineboostbatteryrodr>Stimulated B-Rod</entityname.marineboostbatteryrodr>
	<entitydescription.marineboostbatteryrodr>Increased resistance to paralisis. A powerful rod for an equally powerful suit, rechage it at a charging dock or submarine battery. Although it uses the components from the rod, it doesn't deplete it; instead it uses the elecetronic current from the batteries for most of the heavy lifting.</entitydescription.marineboostbatteryrodr>

	<!-- Helmet container -->
	<entityname.divehelmlockerr>Dive helmet locker</entityname.divehelmlockerr>
	<entitydescription.divehelmlockerr></entitydescription.divehelmlockerr>
	<entityname.largedivehelmlockervr>Large dive helmets locker (vertical)</entityname.largedivehelmlockervr>
	<entitydescription.largedivehelmlockervr></entitydescription.largedivehelmlockervr>
	<entityname.largedivehelmlockerhr>Large dive helmets locker (horizontal)</entityname.largedivehelmlockerhr>
	<entitydescription.largedivehelmlockerhr></entitydescription.largedivehelmlockerhr>
	
</infotexts>